Earth,
before the war.
New York,
before I was born.
A place I have only seen pictures of.
I know you...
But we have never met.
I am with you...
But I don't know your name.
I know I am dreaming.
But it feels like more than that.
It feels like a memory.
How can that be?
March 14th, 2077.
Five years since
the mandatory memory wipe.
And I am still haunted by these dreams.
Victoria and I were assigned together.
In two weeks, our mission here will be
finished,
and we will I join the others.
But the questions I ask,
she doesn't.
The things I wonder about,
she won't.
It's been half a century since
the scavengers destroyed our moon.
Forced to leave their
own dying planet,
they came to take ours.
Without the moon,
the Earth was thrown into chaos.
Earthquakes toppled cities within hours.
Tsunamis wiped out what remained.
Then came the invasion.
We did what we had to do.
We used the nukes.
We won the war,
but lost the planet.
Left it contaminated.
Most of it uninhabitable.
What remained of humanity
had to leave the Earth.
We built the Tet,
our mission control.
A temporary space station
before the migration to Titan,
Saturn's largest moon.
Everyone is there now.
Well,
almost everyone.
Until our tour is complete,
Vika and I do our job.
We protect the hydro rigs,
which convert Earth's sea water
into fusion energy for the new colony.
The survival of humanity depends on it.
Thank you for the coffee.
Remnants of the scavenger army
continue to disrupt the operation.
They attack our drones at night,
and try to kill me during the day.
There is still fight in them,
but I don't know why.
Mission says we have done well.
That we are...
an effective team.
Vika is my communications officer.
She keeps an eye on me.
I handle drone maintenance.
The drones watch everything.
Vika can't wait to go.
Me, I am not so sure.
I can't shake the feeling that Earth,
in spite of all that's happened...
Earth is still my home.
Jack Harper, Tech-49.
Morning Bob.
Tower, comm check.
Drone Maintenance Technician 49,
hydro rig support.
All Bubbleship systems are green.
I am good to go.
Copy, Tech-49, you are cleared.
Be careful out there.
Always am.
No, you are not.
Yeah, you are right.
I got to work on that.
Alright, Tet's coming online in 30 seconds.
Relaying hydro rig coordinates now.
Confirm visual.
I got them.
Hydro rigs are sucking seawater.
You got them, Bob?
Drone 185 looks good.
Jack, we have got two drones down.
Shit.
Stand by, Mission coming online.
And we have Tet contact.
Morning, boss.
Tower 49, this is Mission Control.
How you all doing this lovely morning?
Another day in paradise Sally.
Uploading data now.
49 mission log. Day 1642.
Hydro rig support.
I have two...
You have two drones offline.
Perimeter is compromised.
Copy that, relaying to Tech.
Stand by.
Jack?
166 is down in Grid 37.
Linking to beacon now.
You will go there first.
Got it.
On my way.
Mission, Tech-49 is en route to Grid 37 now.
Can you plug that hole with Drone 109?
Negative, 109 is in the dock.
Still waiting for parts.
Jack better find those drones
and get them flying.
Those rigs can't be exposed overnight.
Copy that.
Tower, didn't he fix 166 recently?
Jack has fixed all the drones recently.
And, if we had the parts
that we have been asking for,
we would not be running
a skeleton crew down here.
Understood.
We are doing the best we can.
Are you an effective team?
We are an effective team.
Your directive today is to rehabilitate 166
and find 172.
Get them flying by sundown,
and I will buy you two a round of
drinks when you get up to the Tet.
You had better be ready Sally.
Two weeks now,
we are keeping track.
Ok.
Come on Bob.
Work with me here buddy.
Tech-49?
Jack?
Copy Tower.
What happened?
I lost you for a second.
Really?
Coming up on location.
There it is.
I have got multiple scav kills.
Drone 166 put up a hell of a fight.
Got any movement?
No sign of scavenger activity but...
I have got limited visibility here Jack,
due to low angle of Mission.
Copy that.
I am coming in hot.
Starting repairs.
Watch my back.
I always do.
You know, I read about this game.
It was played right here.
The last Super Bowl.
Please don't tell me it was a classic.
A classic game.
Down by four.
The ball
was on the 50-yard line.
Seconds left on the clock.
The ball is snapped,
and the QB fumbles.
Disaster.
Looks like the game is over.
I am reading the whole
central core off-alignment.
You don't have the necessary
tools down there.
And a new fuel cell is
not going to fix that.
But this QB runs back,
Jack?
And picks up his own fumble.
Hold on, what did you just do?
There is a wall of linebackers
closing in on him.
So he throws a long ball,
with no idea who is at the other end.
A Hail Mary.
Eighty-thousand people on their feet,
watching this ball sail through the air.
Downfield,
is a rookie...
wide receiver, third string.
He just leaps out of the pack.
Touchdown!
Contact! West contact!
Jack?
It's ok Vika.
It's just a dog.
Hey.
Now go on.
You got to get out of here.
Go on, get!
Get out of here! Go!
Tech-49, Jack Harper.
You are welcome.
166...
is back online.
Two drones shot down today.
Ten fuel cells stolen in just over a month.
These scavs are getting bolder.
Well, the hydro rigs
are taking all the water.
Once we are gone, they will have
nothing but dust and radiation.
This is bullshit.
We won the war.
Now we have to leave.
Two more weeks Jack.
Then we will be on our way to Titan.
Yep.
That drone is out there somewhere.
We just have to find it.
Without a beacon, that's like
finding a needle in a haystack.
So we go to our ground game.
Tower,
located 172,
down a sinkhole.
No visual but I can hear it.
Tet's so far off angle, I can barely see you.
How is it look?
It's good, it's good.
There is no sign of scav activity on top.
Tet is offline in 15 minutes.
After that, you are on your own.
Mission this is Tower 49.
Jack has located drone 172.
Engaged in recovery now.
Requesting backup,
to his location ASAP.
I have got a visual on Drone 172.
Jack?
What the hell?
Shit.
Jack!
Tech-49, Jack Harper.
Jack Harper, Tech-49!
Hey!
Oh, no.
Come on.
Not my goddamn bike!
How can a man die better
Than facing fearful odds
For the ashes of his fathers
And the temples of his Gods
Jack?
Yep,
I will be right there.
How does 109 look?
Can it fly?
Barely.
And without armor, she is a sitting duck.
Well, I will talk to Sally,
about that shielding in the morning.
Again.
What,
Jack Harper?
Where did you get this?
It was growing in...
Come on Jack, you know the regulations.
I know you think I am a stickler
but you have no idea what kind of toxins
could be in something like that.
It's a flower, Vika.
Yeah, that's not the point.
It's that we are so close to the end,
and the last thing that we need
is you putting it all at risk.
Ok.
Every day, you have to go down there,
and see what was lost.
But we have done our job Jack.
It's time to go.
I don't think they were trying to...
kill me today.
The scavs.
They were trying to catch me.
Well, they can't have you.
Come on.
You should come with me sometime,
before we leave.
There is a place I found,
I would like to show you.
I will show you something.
Hey, hey!
Oh, my God.
It was a six-stage meltdown
from inside the hydro rig's core.
It's offline permanently.
Tower 49, you have put
the whole operation at risk.
I need to know exactly what happened.
Jack believes the scavs
weaponized one of the stolen fuel cells
and got it into the suction.
Tower hold.
Tower?
I have got a rogue signal in Grid 37.
Are you seeing this?
Yes.
It's got to be scav.
It's not one of ours.
Jack,
the signal is being directed off-planet.
On my way.
Tower, our logs show you are missing
an additional nine fuel cells.
Can you confirm?
Negative, Mission that number is 10.
Drone 172 was lost last night.
109 is combat ready as soon
as we get that shielding.
We can cover the remaining rigs
with drones in the field.
I have run the numbers.
We will do the numbers up here Tower.
I am tasking the drones to defensive positions.
Copy.
Our job is to run those rigs.
Your directive is to protect them.
We cannot afford to lose another.
Do you copy?
Copy.
Are you and Jack an effective team?
Damn right we are.
Jack?
You are right on top of it.
Do you have a visual?
Jack?
Yeah,
I got it.
They have some kind of a repeater.
The scavs...
are using the building,
as an antenna.
Can you decrypt?
It's a set of coordinates.
Grid 17.
It's a goddamn homing beacon.
What the hell is out there?
Nothing.
It's the middle of nowhere.
What is going on?
Why would the scavs send
a signal off-planet Jack?
I am shutting it down.
Tech-49, check your course.
You are headed right for the border.
That radiation will cook you from
the inside before you know it.
It's ok Vika.
I see it.
I am gonna do a...
perimeter check,
before I head home.
I may go off-comm.
Jack, we should keep in contact.
Just let me know where you are.
Do you copy?
Jack do you copy?
That's right Bob.
You know where we are going.
Are you gonna miss me?
I am gonna miss this place.
It would have been great.
Vika? Vika, did you get that?
Jack, where have you been?
An object came down in 17.
That's the beacon coordinates.
Exactly.
I saw it.
Some sort of vessel.
Jack, Mission is almost offline.
I am en route now.
Mission, we have an unidentified
object impact in 17.
It came down at coordinates
sent by a scav beacon.
My tech is en route now.
Tower, we are going offline soon but...
but drones are already
mobile and executing.
Have your tech stand down.
Copy.
Jack, Mission wants you to stand down.
The drones will handle it.
That's a negative Tower.
With Tet offline, we need our eyes on this.
I want to know this site is secure.
Sally, my tech is concerned about
the security of the site.
Tower, you have lost
enough assets for today.
Keep your tech out of there.
Do you copy?
Copy, Command I am...
Jack, Command wants you to stand down.
The drones will handle this.
I am on site.
Jack.
I don't have eyes on you.
Command is offline.
Vika,
I think it's one of ours.
This thing is ancient.
It looks...
pre-war.
The scavs brought this thing down, Jack.
There is no sign of scavs.
Technician, this is your Control.
I am ordering you to pull out,
and return to the tower immediately.
Touching down.
They are human.
Tower,
we have got survivors.
There are four.
Check it, five survivors.
They are human.
Stand down!
Vika, the drones are firing on survivors.
Jack, the Tet is offline, I-I...
I don't have control.
Stand down!
Jack Harper, Tech-49.
Back off, you son of a bitch!
Back off!
Open the door.
Vika!
Get the med kit.
Get the med kit!
This has to be reported.
Be sure and report that the drones
killed the crew from one of our own ships.
See what Command makes of that.
It's breathing fluid.
Just let her get it out.
Jack.
Here. You are still dehydrated.
Where are we?
I am Victoria,
this is Jack.
What's your name?
I am Julia.
Julia...
I am sorry for what I have to tell you,
but you were in a crash.
Your ship came down.
Jack managed to pull you
from the wreckage.
But none of your crew survived.
What do you mean?
You are the only one that made it.
I am sorry.
You have been in delta sleep for a long time.
Some disorientation is normal.
How long?
Sixty years.
At least.
I have to get back to our ship.
It's too dangerous down there.
You need to rest.
Vika...
Don't touch me.
Your ship's re-entry was triggered
by a beacon...
from the surface.
Do you know anything about that?
What was your mission?
It's classified.
Well, we have no record of an Odyssey...
I can't tell you anything until I get
the flight recorder from my ship.
Julia,
a lot has changed in 60 years.
While you were in delta sleep,
Earth was attacked.
Call them scavs.
They destroyed our moon
and with that half...
the planet.
Then they invaded.
We won the war,
but Earth was ruined.
Everyone is on Titan now.
It's a moon of Saturn or on the...
space station, getting ready to go.
We are here for security
and drone maintenance.
We are the mop-up crew.
You have lost people.
Everything.
If you want to be alone,
we understand.
The drones...
killed her entire crew.
If I had not gotten there...
I want her gone first thing.
Vika?
Do you have any memories...
before the mission?
Before the security wipe?
Our job is not to remember.
Remember?
Do you remember her?
Jack...
That was a scav beacon
that brought her down.
We don't know who she is.
Or what she is.
Let's just get through the night.
Ok?
You fly that thing?
Yes.
What happens now?
The Tet will be online soon.
Victoria,
will report your rescue.
They will send someone down for you.
From the Tet?
Yes.
I need to get the flight recorder
from my ship.
The scavs, they move at night.
They could be all over it by now.
I need to know what happened.
You need to know what happened.
Please.
Jack?
What are you doing?
Vika, she is a flight officer.
She wants to see her ship
and secure the flight recorder.
Now, you would want the same thing.
Jack I...
can't protect you.
No I understand.
This one is on me.
I could not save them.
Jack.
Jack!
Jack, can you hear me?
Alright, it's time to go.
Jack.
I found it.
Jack!
Tower 49, how are you
all this lovely morning?
Another day in paradise.
Sally...
Jack...
took a pre-dawn patrol
and...
went off-comm
near the canyons in 17.
Now I know,
I know we are low on drones,
but...
requesting one to sweep the area.
Just a quick scout.
Copy 49,
tasking 185 to Grid 22.
And how can a man die better
Than facing fearful odds
For the ashes of his fathers
And the temples of his Gods
I have been watching you, Jack.
You are curious.
What are you looking for in those books?
Do they bring back old memories?
You won't get anything from me.
My memory has been wiped,
to protect the security...
the security of the mission, yes.
You can't have your precious memory
falling into the wrong hands,
now can you?
Tell me.
Have you ever met a...
scav...
up close?
Of course not.
You just repair drones.
Don't go into the radiation zone.
Don't ask too many questions.
Not part of the...
job description.
Lights.
We are not alien, Jack.
We are human.
Of course for us,
being human is a problem.
Old stealth fighter tech.
Shields us from your scanners.
Vocal scrambling.
Can you hear me Jack?
Keeps your drones confused.
Well,
most of the time.
The drones are programmed...
To kill humans Jack.
You saw what they did
to those sleep pods.
You almost got yourself,
blown
to bits protecting that woman.
Why did you do that?
Anyone would have.
Anyone.
Interesting.
We are wasting our time.
The drone will track him here.
That's Sergeant Sykes.
He thinks I am a fool
for having brought you here.
I hope you prove him wrong.
Mission, I am picking up a bio trail
somewhere near the west canyons.
Can you confirm the sequence?
Stand by.
DNA confirmed.
It's Jack.
Vika, are you ok?
Everything good between you two?
Of course.
You are still an effective team?
We are great.
Never better.
We were running a ground game,
and losing.
So we decided, what the hell?
We have got to throw the long ball.
It took us decades just
to crack the GPS codes.
That's how you brought down the Odyssey.
Why?
The Odyssey is compact reactor,
courtesy of NASA.
Very hard to come by.
Did you like the show last night?
That was just one fuel cell.
Imagine what 10 of them will do,
with a core...
of weapons-grade plutonium.
We have a nuke,
and we have a drone to carry it.
But we can't access it.
It doesn't know who we are.
But it knows you Jack.
We need you to program the drone.
Have it carry our nuke up to the Tet.
End this war.
There are people up there.
Sergeant.
Program the drone to return to the Tet.
It needs to go right to the center.
Screw you.
We have not got time for this.
Hey. Hey!
No.
Let's go!
Get him up.
Mission,
185 just went off-grid.
Copy Tower, we are seeing the same thing.
Permission to task two additional drones?
If one drone is here,
more will come.
And they won't stop until they find me.
They will turn this place to dust.
But if you let us go,
I will call them off.
It's your only chance.
I have been to your...
radiation zones.
If you are looking for the truth,
that's where you will find it.
You have risked all our lives.
Everything.
What makes you think he is different?
She does.
Mission,
I have found my tech over in 37.
You can call off the search.
Copy that Tower.
Glad Jack is safe.
Tasking the other drones back
to rig support.
Where are we going now?
Who are you?
What are not you telling me?
Jack I...
What were you doing on the Odyssey?
What was your mission?
It was a research flight to Titan.
My first.
That's what it was supposed to be.
Six weeks to launch, deep space
scanners picked up an alien object.
We were reassigned to investigate.
They put us all in delta.
They must have...
woken you and Victoria first.
What?
That object...
was the Tet Jack.
The Tet...
was our mission.
That's impossible.
That's impossible!
Who are you?
I am your wife.
I don't know what happened,
but you are not who you think you are.
Jack, we were here.
You asked me to meet you,
brought me up on top of the world.
I could tell you were nervous that day.
It was right here Jack.
You said,
Look through here,
and I will show you the future.
And I held up a ring.
And you said...
Yes.
There you are.
Hi.
Hello.
Come on.
Vika, I am coming in.
Do not report to Mission until I get back.
Do you copy?
Vika,
open the door.
Stay away from me.
I don't want to hear it.
It's not safe here,
and we need to leave, now.
It was always her.
Was not it?
Vika...
She is my wife.
Mission, this is Tower 49.
Go ahead 49.
No.
I am having a problem with my technician.
No, you don't know what you are doing.
He found a survivor at the crash site.
You have got to listen to me.
She is impeding his abilities,
and he is unfit for service.
No, no, no, no.
I am sorry to hear that Vika.
Are you still an effective team?
Vika...
Open the goddamn door, Vika!
No.
We are not an effective team.
Vika please.
We have to go now.
I am not,
I am not going
anywhere with you Jack.
There is a place I know.
We will be safe.
I am going to Titan.
There is no Titan.
They lied to us.
Just stay away from me.
Vika,
please,
there are things...
Things you need to know.
I don't want to know!
Jack...
Hi Jack.
I don't believe
we have had the pleasure.
What have you done?
You can't blame yourself for this.
Drones are unreliable.
Sometimes things go wrong.
Go wrong?
You killed her.
I know,
it's tragic.
She was a wonderful person.
Jack,
we want to bring you in.
I have been authorized to tell you
we are going to assign you
a new mission.
You and the survivor.
There is a lot of interest up here.
Bring her up.
We can debrief,
then anything is possible.
It's time to come home Jack.
Jack?
Jack...
I am sorry.
Hang on.
Lightning.
That's the plan.
We need cover.
There.
Are you ok?
No.
Don't worry, we are staying out of there.
Are we gonna die?
No!
Maybe.
Jack!
Son of a bitch.
Wait here.
Who is it?
Hey!
Wait!
Drop your weapon!
It's...
It's ok.
Don't move!
We have to shut that drone...
down.
Stop moving!
Jack!
It's ok.
Julia.
Julia!
Don't.
Don't touch me.
Hold on.
Just hold on.
Jack Harper,
Tech-52.
Hey.
There you are.
What happened?
Are you ok?
That bogey came across the border
and then I lost you.
False alarm.
I should get back out there.
You come all the way home,
and I don't get a kiss?
What's going on up there?
I was thinking...
Why don't you come down with me?
To the surface?
We could go right now.
Now?
Yeah.
Are you serious?
You won't believe what's down there.
Jack...
You know the regulations.
Yes.
Can we not do this again?
I am done talking about it.
Ok.
This is gonna hurt.
Hell of a day Bob?
You always loved this song.
I am not him.
I know I am not.
But I have loved you...
for as long as I can remember.
I don't know how else to say it.
You know what you said to me once?
You said when it was all over, you
would build me a house on a lake.
We would grow old and...
fat together.
And we would fight.
Maybe drink too much.
Real romantic.
And then we would die...
and be buried in a meadow by the lake.
And the world would forget about us.
But we would always have each other.
I remember.
Those memories are yours, Jack.
They are ours.
They are you.
Good morning.
I wanted to spend
the rest of my life here.
You still can.
I have to go.
Those people need my help.
We will come back when it's over.
Promise me.
You had me worried for a second.
I thought you were not coming back.
Well, I had to prove him wrong.
You look like shit.
You should see the other guy.
If I had told you
what you would find out there,
you would have thought I was crazy.
I still do.
Malcolm Beech.
Julia Harper.
Come on.
Mission, I am picking up a bio-trail
somewhere near the West Canyons.
Can you confirm the sequence?
Stand by.
DNA confirmed, it's Jack.
Mission,
185 just went off-grid.
Copy, Tower.
We are seeing the same thing.
I had been in the army less than a year
when that unholy Tet arrived.
I saw the moon get taken out.
Right up there in the night sky.
I could not believe it.
After that, nature took over.
There is bedrock around Chicago,
so we were spared the worst
of the waves and the quakes.
Most people just starved.
Then the Tet sent troop ships down.
The doors opened,
and out you came.
Astronaut Jack Harper.
Thousands of you.
Memory wiped.
Programmed to kill.
They had taken one of our best...
and turned him against us.
No soul.
No humanity.
The Tet.
What a brilliant machine.
Feeding off one planet
after another for energy.
Phase Two...
was drones.
Repairmen.
50 years of watching those...
hydro rigs suck our planet dry.
Then one day,
I saw you set down.
Another drone to fix.
But in the rubble that day,
was a book.
You picked it up.
You studied it.
And I...
thought I saw a way.
When you stepped in front of
that drone,
and saved her,
I knew.
You were in there,
somewhere.
I just had to find a way
to bring you back.
Watch... watch off.
Eyes on it.
Steady.
Give it some space.
Come on, you are making it nervous.
That is one pissed-off weapon.
No,
it's just a machine.
I am the weapon.
I would love to be there to see
that thing's face when this goes off.
That would be a one-way trip.
Yeah,
but it would be worth it.
Welcome back Commander.
Open the doors!
Shit!
Spread out!
Head down, keep your head down!
Jack!
Follow me!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
Hey!
Jack.
I am ok.
The drone.
Send the drone.
It's gone.
I thought we had it.
I really did.
I can take the bomb myself.
You know it will swat you like a fly.
Not if I go.
No.
She asked you to bring me up.
So bring me up.
We will go together.
It reminds me of home.
Ready?
Jack.
Dream of us.
Jack...
Flight recorder,
playback for the Odyssey mission.
3 May, 2017.
Ok Bob.
Ready for space?
Good morning Odyssey,
from your friends here at Mission Control.
Good morning Mission.
This is Commander Jack Harper.
Thank you for that fantastic wake-up call.
Pre-rendezvous checks complete.
Electrical guidance
and nav systems, all good.
Range behind object,
250 clicks...
12 below V-bar, closure rate
200 kilometers per hour.
Copy that.
It's good to see you Jack.
After 39 days of sleep,
sounds like you are ready to go.
I am ready to go.
Your next burn will bring you up level
and co-speed at 50 kilometer
range, where you will hold.
Copy.
We will hold 50 clicks from object
for sensor scan and evaluation.
Targets look good.
Initiating burn in three...
Two...
One...
Ignition.
We see a good burn.
Are you reading any output
from the object?
Negative.
Zero heat.
No EMR.
There is no sign of life.
How is the rest of the crew doing?
Co-pilot Victoria Olsen
should be up here shortly.
The rest of the crew...
remains in delta sleep.
Copy that.
You missed a hell of a game last night.
What did I tell you guys?
No spoilers about last night's game.
I am looking forward
to watching it when I get back.
You are not talking about
football already, are you?
Good morning Vika.
Good morning Sally.
How are you doing this lovely morning?
Another day in paradise.
Hey.
One for history.
Yeah.
Tech-49,
I have you on approach.
Hello Sally.
It's a busy morning?
I am picking up a second passenger, Jack.
It's Julia Rusakova,
the female survivor from the crashed module.
State your intention.
Deliver the survivor,
as requested.
We are...
a more effective team.
Proceed to entry.
Mission we have a...
situation.
The last burn was spot-on to give
us a 50-click hold from object,
but radar range still decreasing.
We are accelerating toward the object.
We are going to need
full OMS burn to pull away.
Initiate now.
Entering target.
Gimbals set.
Target is good.
Arm forward engines.
Engines on.
Ready?
Let's go.
Mission, we are in full OMS burn,
trying to back out.
There is a lot of vibration.
We are not getting away from this thing.
Odyssey,
telemetry shows
structural overstress.
Knock off the burn.
Do you copy?
Cutting off burn.
Mission.
Mission?
Sally?
Increased acceleration toward the object.
Estimated contact within two minutes.
I am going to eject the sleep module.
It's programmed for reinsertion
into Earth orbit.
I will fly the Command module out
if I break free.
I want you back there now.
Absolutely not.
That's an order!
Jack?
No, we are a team.
We have got to go, Jack! 30 seconds!
Dream of us.
Jack...
Tech-49, enter at headway speed.
Entering at headway.
You buck up, Bob.
Don't go all shaky on me.
Jack, I can't help notice
your respiration
and heart rate have increased.
I am just excited to finally meet you Sally.
There is been a pattern of
insubordinate behavior recently.
Yeah.
I feel bad about that.
Voice analysis indicates
you are lying to me Jack.
Tell me why you are here.
You have five seconds.
I want Julia to live.
I want our species to survive.
This is the only way.
Proceed to landing.
Atmosphere provided.
Welcome home Jack.
Come on.
Jack, you are doing the right thing.
I don't know what you are,
or where you are from but...
I would like to tell you about something I read.
A story...
from Rome,
a city you destroyed.
It's a classic.
There was a guy,
Horatius,
held the bridge alone against a whole army.
And what Horatius said was,
How can a man die better...
You don't have to die Jack.
She doesn't have to die.
Everybody dies Sally.
The thing is, to die well.
Jack,
that's not the survivor you promised me.
No, it's not.
What...
Horatius said was,
How...
can a man die better.
Than facing fearful odds,
Drones!
Get inside! Get inside!
For the ashes of his fathers
And the temples of his Gods
I created you Jack.
I am your God.
Fuck you Sally.
Earth,
after the war.
Three years have passed
since I saw your face.
I wonder if I come to you,
at night,
in dreams.
In the day,
as memories.
Do I haunt your hours,
the way you haunted mine?
And I wonder if you see me,
when you look at her.
Mommy look.
If we have souls,
they are made of the love we share.
Undimmed by time.
Unbound by death.
For three years,
I searched for the house he built.
I knew it had to be out there.
Because I know him.
I am him.
Who is that?
I am Jack Harper.
And I am home.
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections August 2022